Yujun.
I like you.
Enough to give you my everything.
I said that's enough.
When did you wake up?
Since you started staring at me.
I have to head out early.
You still have time.
I have a first-period class today.
And Professor Han asked me for a favor.
Happy?
That felt a bit obligatory, don't you think?
I'll come home early.
Are you dropping me off again?
Yeah, of course.
So hurry up and wash up.
Hurry.
Go on.
Don't you get tired of dropping me off every time?
I can go by myself.
I'm dropping you off, why would I be tired?
Your unemployed boyfriend should at least be your chauffeur.
What do you mean, unemployed?
You're just taking a short break.
Hmm?
It's going to scab over.
You're the one who did it.
I told you not to.
This is my only joy these days.
(Jiseok) I'm ready.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Kim Yeonho.
Later.
I'll tell you later.
You're going to be late.
Are you really not going to tell me?
Whatever you're thinking,
or whatever you're worrying about,
it's not like that.
I'm not cheating on you.
Who else would I look at besides you?
Who said anything about cheating?
It was written all over your face.
Hurry up and go.
Yeah, I'm going.
Yeah.
I'll come pick you up tonight.
When should we meet?
The sooner the better for me.
Since it's you I'm seeing, Yeonho.
What will you say?
How will you react?
It doesn't even show.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Kim Yeonho.
Later.
I'll tell you later.
You said you'd be a cool boyfriend.
Why can't you be cool?
As if Kim Yeonho would ever cheat.
Come in.
Here are the materials you asked for.
You could have just emailed them.
The file size was too big.
And I wanted an excuse to see you, Professor.
I'm a fan of yours, Professor.
I read the thesis you published as a grad student,
and applied to this school because of it.
Could I ask for your autograph?
Is it really worth getting an autograph?
Of course.
It even made me want to become a grad student.
Aren't you still a freshman, Sueon?
That's right.
But if I could work with you, Professor,
I'm more than ready to become a grad student.
The research materials on AI technology...
...are fun to read no matter how many times I read them.
You're the first person I've met...
...who found it fun to read.
By the way, where did you get this book?
It was really hard to find.
You didn't print that many copies.
Right.
Because there aren't many people who would buy...
...a thesis book published by a grad student.
Should I sign here?
Yes. Thank you.
Yes?
Yeonho.
Hello.
I don't think we've met properly.
You know Yeonho?
I've seen him drop you off in the mornings,
so I guess I felt a sense of familiarity.
I saw you getting out of his car.
He's a friend, right?
Yes, he's a friend.
Here's your book.
You should get going now.
Thank you.
See you next time.
Yujun.
Don't even touch me when we're outside.
Yujun...
Go home.
I have a class, so I have to go.
Seriously.
I promise.
I really won't lay a hand on you.
Alright.
I was thinking we could go on a date today.
Go inside and sleep.
I thought you said you wouldn't touch me.
But we're at home.
This is way better than a date.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Suddenly?
Where are you going?
Someone asked to see me.
I'll be back soon.
Right now?
Understood.
Yes.
Go to sleep first if I'm late.